{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549111304172","data":{"timestamp":" 1549111304172"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" 421efb55-ba99-40d3-ac46-4e8a97078efb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_jo_di-jo-wi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" jo"," userResponse":" jo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549111310062","data":{"timestamp":" 1549111310062"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" 421efb55-ba99-40d3-ac46-4e8a97078efb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ga_pe-ti-ga"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ga"," userResponse":" ga"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549111315440","data":{"timestamp":" 1549111315439"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" 421efb55-ba99-40d3-ac46-4e8a97078efb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_po_po-no-da"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" po"," userResponse":" po"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549111320612","data":{"timestamp":" 1549111320612"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" 421efb55-ba99-40d3-ac46-4e8a97078efb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ho_ho-sa-mu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ho"," userResponse":" ho"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549111325017","data":{"timestamp":" 1549111325016"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" 421efb55-ba99-40d3-ac46-4e8a97078efb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pi_pi-zo-we"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pi"," userResponse":" pi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549111330284","data":{"timestamp":" 1549111330284"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" 421efb55-ba99-40d3-ac46-4e8a97078efb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pu_du-pu-ta"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pu"," userResponse":" pu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549111335039","data":{"timestamp":" 1549111335039"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" 421efb55-ba99-40d3-ac46-4e8a97078efb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ze_ku-wa-ze"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ze"," userResponse":" ze"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549111344900","data":{"timestamp":" 1549111344900"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" 421efb55-ba99-40d3-ac46-4e8a97078efb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_de_pe-ha-de"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" de"," userResponse":" de"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549111350745","data":{"timestamp":" 1549111350744"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" 421efb55-ba99-40d3-ac46-4e8a97078efb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_wu_zo-wu-ja"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wu"," userResponse":" wu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549111359903","data":{"timestamp":" 1549111359902"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" 421efb55-ba99-40d3-ac46-4e8a97078efb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_wu_zo-wu-ja"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549111377475","data":{"timestamp":" 1549111377475"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" 7eaa866e-f170-4ae0-b677-3a3c9af85957"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ga_pe-ti-ga"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ga"," userResponse":" ga"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549111382679","data":{"timestamp":" 1549111382679"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" 7eaa866e-f170-4ae0-b677-3a3c9af85957"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pi_pi-zo-we"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pi"," userResponse":" pi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549111391587","data":{"timestamp":" 1549111391587"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" 7eaa866e-f170-4ae0-b677-3a3c9af85957"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_de_pe-ha-de"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" de"," userResponse":" de"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549111398490","data":{"timestamp":" 1549111398490"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" 7eaa866e-f170-4ae0-b677-3a3c9af85957"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_wu_zo-wu-ja"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wu"," userResponse":" wu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549111403804","data":{"timestamp":" 1549111403803"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" 7eaa866e-f170-4ae0-b677-3a3c9af85957"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_jo_di-jo-wi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" jo"," userResponse":" jo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549111410786","data":{"timestamp":" 1549111410786"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" 7eaa866e-f170-4ae0-b677-3a3c9af85957"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pu_du-pu-ta"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pu"," userResponse":" pu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549111416624","data":{"timestamp":" 1549111416624"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" 7eaa866e-f170-4ae0-b677-3a3c9af85957"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ho_ho-sa-mu"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ho"," userResponse":" ho"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549111423184","data":{"timestamp":" 1549111423184"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" 7eaa866e-f170-4ae0-b677-3a3c9af85957"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ze_ku-wa-ze"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ze"," userResponse":" ze"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549111427925","data":{"timestamp":" 1549111427925"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" 7eaa866e-f170-4ae0-b677-3a3c9af85957"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_po_po-no-da"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" po"," userResponse":" po"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549111434089","data":{"timestamp":" 1549111434089"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" 7eaa866e-f170-4ae0-b677-3a3c9af85957"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ji_je-ji-si"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ji"," userResponse":" ji"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549111439870","data":{"timestamp":" 1549111439869"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" 7eaa866e-f170-4ae0-b677-3a3c9af85957"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_ji_je-ji-si"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549111457674","data":{"timestamp":" 1549111457674"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" 44241aab-ca8d-4e32-b7d4-3dcbc14f3307"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ga_pe-ti-ga"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ga"," userResponse":" ga"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549111462578","data":{"timestamp":" 1549111462578"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" 44241aab-ca8d-4e32-b7d4-3dcbc14f3307"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ji_je-ji-si"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ji"," userResponse":" ji"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549111467157","data":{"timestamp":" 1549111467157"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" 44241aab-ca8d-4e32-b7d4-3dcbc14f3307"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ho_ho-sa-mu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ho"," userResponse":" ho"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549111472472","data":{"timestamp":" 1549111472471"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" 44241aab-ca8d-4e32-b7d4-3dcbc14f3307"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pi_pi-zo-we"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pi"," userResponse":" pi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549111481571","data":{"timestamp":" 1549111481571"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" 44241aab-ca8d-4e32-b7d4-3dcbc14f3307"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_de_pe-ha-de"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" de"," userResponse":" de"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549111491279","data":{"timestamp":" 1549111491278"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" 44241aab-ca8d-4e32-b7d4-3dcbc14f3307"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_wu_zo-wu-ja"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wu"," userResponse":" wu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549111499786","data":{"timestamp":" 1549111499786"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" 44241aab-ca8d-4e32-b7d4-3dcbc14f3307"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_po_po-no-da"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" po"," userResponse":" po"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549111508230","data":{"timestamp":" 1549111508230"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" 44241aab-ca8d-4e32-b7d4-3dcbc14f3307"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pu_du-pu-ta"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pu"," userResponse":" pu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549111515422","data":{"timestamp":" 1549111515422"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" 44241aab-ca8d-4e32-b7d4-3dcbc14f3307"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_jo_di-jo-wi"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" jo"," userResponse":" jo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549111522286","data":{"timestamp":" 1549111522286"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" 44241aab-ca8d-4e32-b7d4-3dcbc14f3307"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ze_ku-wa-ze"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ze"," userResponse":" ze"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549111528047","data":{"timestamp":" 1549111528047"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" 44241aab-ca8d-4e32-b7d4-3dcbc14f3307"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_ze_ku-wa-ze"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549111548246","data":{"timestamp":" 1549111548246"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" 418e6b36-e710-465b-a575-4b2a6b93df91"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ga_pe-ti-ga"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ga"," userResponse":" ga"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549111553931","data":{"timestamp":" 1549111553931"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" 418e6b36-e710-465b-a575-4b2a6b93df91"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_wu_zo-wu-ja"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wu"," userResponse":" ja"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549111563454","data":{"timestamp":" 1549111563454"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" 418e6b36-e710-465b-a575-4b2a6b93df91"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_wu_zo-wu-ja"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wu"," userResponse":" wu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549111565861","data":{"timestamp":" 1549111565860"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" 418e6b36-e710-465b-a575-4b2a6b93df91"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_wu_zo-wu-ja"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549111576426","data":{"timestamp":" 1549111576425"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" 418e6b36-e710-465b-a575-4b2a6b93df91"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_wu_zo-wu-ja"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549111587286","data":{"timestamp":" 1549111587286"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" 418e6b36-e710-465b-a575-4b2a6b93df91"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_wu_zo-wu-ja"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549111601074","data":{"timestamp":" 1549111601073"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" aef1f0c7-dd54-4e7a-a946-64aaae0f36c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ji_je-ji-si"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ji"," userResponse":" ji"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549111607293","data":{"timestamp":" 1549111607293"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" aef1f0c7-dd54-4e7a-a946-64aaae0f36c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pi_pi-zo-we"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pi"," userResponse":" pi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549111611079","data":{"timestamp":" 1549111611078"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" aef1f0c7-dd54-4e7a-a946-64aaae0f36c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_pi_pi-zo-we"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549113461807","data":{"timestamp":" 1549113461807"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" b32e7008-cf86-4ca0-a0f5-ff1348f101ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_3-4-7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549113469466","data":{"timestamp":" 1549113469466"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" b32e7008-cf86-4ca0-a0f5-ff1348f101ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-2-7"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549113475294","data":{"timestamp":" 1549113475294"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" b32e7008-cf86-4ca0-a0f5-ff1348f101ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_8-10-5"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549113481104","data":{"timestamp":" 1549113481104"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" b32e7008-cf86-4ca0-a0f5-ff1348f101ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_11-13-7"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549113487130","data":{"timestamp":" 1549113487129"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" b32e7008-cf86-4ca0-a0f5-ff1348f101ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_8-3-5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549113493236","data":{"timestamp":" 1549113493236"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" b32e7008-cf86-4ca0-a0f5-ff1348f101ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_8-10-7"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549113499093","data":{"timestamp":" 1549113499093"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" b32e7008-cf86-4ca0-a0f5-ff1348f101ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_2-12-5"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549113504736","data":{"timestamp":" 1549113504736"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" b32e7008-cf86-4ca0-a0f5-ff1348f101ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-5-6"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549113514361","data":{"timestamp":" 1549113514361"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" b32e7008-cf86-4ca0-a0f5-ff1348f101ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_10-2-4"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549113522403","data":{"timestamp":" 1549113522403"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" b32e7008-cf86-4ca0-a0f5-ff1348f101ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_2-11-7"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 11"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549113530389","data":{"timestamp":" 1549113530388"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" b32e7008-cf86-4ca0-a0f5-ff1348f101ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_2-11-7"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549113537112","data":{"timestamp":" 1549113537112"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" b32e7008-cf86-4ca0-a0f5-ff1348f101ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_7_2-11-7"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.fu..fu.noShow..15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549113565368","data":{"timestamp":" 1549113565368"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" 1b8210a8-9523-4787-af93-5a325e155166"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.fu..fu.noShow..15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_fa_fo_fi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.fu..fu.noShow..15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549113572094","data":{"timestamp":" 1549113572093"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" 1b8210a8-9523-4787-af93-5a325e155166"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.fu..fu.noShow..15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_fi_fo_fu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.fu..fu.noShow..15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549113578825","data":{"timestamp":" 1549113578825"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" 1b8210a8-9523-4787-af93-5a325e155166"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.fu..fu.noShow..15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_fi_fu_fe"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.fu..fu.noShow..15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549113585552","data":{"timestamp":" 1549113585552"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" 1b8210a8-9523-4787-af93-5a325e155166"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.fu..fu.noShow..15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_fe_fu_fi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.fu..fu.noShow..15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549113592241","data":{"timestamp":" 1549113592241"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" 1b8210a8-9523-4787-af93-5a325e155166"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.fu..fu.noShow..15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_fi_fa_fo"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.fu..fu.noShow..15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549113598953","data":{"timestamp":" 1549113598953"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" 1b8210a8-9523-4787-af93-5a325e155166"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.fu..fu.noShow..15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_fo_fu_fe"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.fu..fu.noShow..15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549113606527","data":{"timestamp":" 1549113606527"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" 1b8210a8-9523-4787-af93-5a325e155166"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.fu..fu.noShow..15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_fo_fu_fe"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.fu..fu.noShow..15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549113613292","data":{"timestamp":" 1549113613292"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" 1b8210a8-9523-4787-af93-5a325e155166"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.fu..fu.noShow..15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_fa_fe_fo"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.fu..fu.noShow..15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549113619950","data":{"timestamp":" 1549113619949"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" 1b8210a8-9523-4787-af93-5a325e155166"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.fu..fu.noShow..15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_fu_fi_fe"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.fu..fu.noShow..15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549113626661","data":{"timestamp":" 1549113626661"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" 1b8210a8-9523-4787-af93-5a325e155166"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.fu..fu.noShow..15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_fi_fo_fu"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.fu..fu.noShow..15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549113633367","data":{"timestamp":" 1549113633367"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" 1b8210a8-9523-4787-af93-5a325e155166"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.fu..fu.noShow..15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_fo_fi_fu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.fu..fu.noShow..15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549113640891","data":{"timestamp":" 1549113640891"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" 1b8210a8-9523-4787-af93-5a325e155166"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.fu..fu.noShow..15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_fo_fi_fu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.fu..fu.noShow..15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549113653985","data":{"timestamp":" 1549113653985"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" 1b8210a8-9523-4787-af93-5a325e155166"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.fu..fu.noShow..15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_fo_fi_fu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549113671739","data":{"timestamp":" 1549113671739"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" 1350b1c7-5de1-4cd1-9242-a17a1ce8f645"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549113671971","data":{"timestamp":" 1549113671971"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" 1350b1c7-5de1-4cd1-9242-a17a1ce8f645"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549113672935","data":{"timestamp":" 1549113672935"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" 1350b1c7-5de1-4cd1-9242-a17a1ce8f645"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549113674222","data":{"timestamp":" 1549113674221"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" 1350b1c7-5de1-4cd1-9242-a17a1ce8f645"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549113677099","data":{"timestamp":" 1549113677099"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" 1350b1c7-5de1-4cd1-9242-a17a1ce8f645"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549113681074","data":{"timestamp":" 1549113681073"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" 1350b1c7-5de1-4cd1-9242-a17a1ce8f645"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549113684755","data":{"timestamp":" 1549113684755"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" 1350b1c7-5de1-4cd1-9242-a17a1ce8f645"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549113684801","data":{"timestamp":" 1549113684801"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" 1350b1c7-5de1-4cd1-9242-a17a1ce8f645"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549113684923","data":{"timestamp":" 1549113684923"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" 1350b1c7-5de1-4cd1-9242-a17a1ce8f645"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549113696318","data":{"timestamp":" 1549113696318"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" a863c263-8bd4-41b9-884c-b2bf6aa2da1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549113696560","data":{"timestamp":" 1549113696560"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" a863c263-8bd4-41b9-884c-b2bf6aa2da1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549113697525","data":{"timestamp":" 1549113697525"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" a863c263-8bd4-41b9-884c-b2bf6aa2da1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549113698799","data":{"timestamp":" 1549113698799"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" a863c263-8bd4-41b9-884c-b2bf6aa2da1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549113701689","data":{"timestamp":" 1549113701689"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" a863c263-8bd4-41b9-884c-b2bf6aa2da1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549113702533","data":{"timestamp":" 1549113702533"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" a863c263-8bd4-41b9-884c-b2bf6aa2da1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549113702848","data":{"timestamp":" 1549113702848"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" a863c263-8bd4-41b9-884c-b2bf6aa2da1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549113704082","data":{"timestamp":" 1549113704082"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" a863c263-8bd4-41b9-884c-b2bf6aa2da1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549113707604","data":{"timestamp":" 1549113707604"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" a863c263-8bd4-41b9-884c-b2bf6aa2da1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549113708589","data":{"timestamp":" 1549113708589"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" a863c263-8bd4-41b9-884c-b2bf6aa2da1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549113708844","data":{"timestamp":" 1549113708843"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" a863c263-8bd4-41b9-884c-b2bf6aa2da1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549113709787","data":{"timestamp":" 1549113709787"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" a863c263-8bd4-41b9-884c-b2bf6aa2da1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549113712656","data":{"timestamp":" 1549113712656"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" a863c263-8bd4-41b9-884c-b2bf6aa2da1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549113713689","data":{"timestamp":" 1549113713689"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" a863c263-8bd4-41b9-884c-b2bf6aa2da1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549113714162","data":{"timestamp":" 1549113714162"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" a863c263-8bd4-41b9-884c-b2bf6aa2da1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549113718723","data":{"timestamp":" 1549113718723"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" a863c263-8bd4-41b9-884c-b2bf6aa2da1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549113718876","data":{"timestamp":" 1549113718876"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" a863c263-8bd4-41b9-884c-b2bf6aa2da1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549113730583","data":{"timestamp":" 1549113730579"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" 40fb569e-ea12-4cd7-be2b-0fcd50886535"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549113730811","data":{"timestamp":" 1549113730811"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" 40fb569e-ea12-4cd7-be2b-0fcd50886535"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549113731776","data":{"timestamp":" 1549113731776"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" 40fb569e-ea12-4cd7-be2b-0fcd50886535"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549113733051","data":{"timestamp":" 1549113733050"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" 40fb569e-ea12-4cd7-be2b-0fcd50886535"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549113735903","data":{"timestamp":" 1549113735902"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" 40fb569e-ea12-4cd7-be2b-0fcd50886535"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549113736746","data":{"timestamp":" 1549113736746"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" 40fb569e-ea12-4cd7-be2b-0fcd50886535"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549113737060","data":{"timestamp":" 1549113737060"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" 40fb569e-ea12-4cd7-be2b-0fcd50886535"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549113738294","data":{"timestamp":" 1549113738294"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" 40fb569e-ea12-4cd7-be2b-0fcd50886535"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549113741846","data":{"timestamp":" 1549113741846"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" 40fb569e-ea12-4cd7-be2b-0fcd50886535"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549113742835","data":{"timestamp":" 1549113742835"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" 40fb569e-ea12-4cd7-be2b-0fcd50886535"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549113743090","data":{"timestamp":" 1549113743090"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" 40fb569e-ea12-4cd7-be2b-0fcd50886535"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549113744034","data":{"timestamp":" 1549113744034"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" 40fb569e-ea12-4cd7-be2b-0fcd50886535"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549113746899","data":{"timestamp":" 1549113746899"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" 40fb569e-ea12-4cd7-be2b-0fcd50886535"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549113747933","data":{"timestamp":" 1549113747933"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" 40fb569e-ea12-4cd7-be2b-0fcd50886535"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549113748411","data":{"timestamp":" 1549113748410"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" 40fb569e-ea12-4cd7-be2b-0fcd50886535"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549113752959","data":{"timestamp":" 1549113752958"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" 40fb569e-ea12-4cd7-be2b-0fcd50886535"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549113753067","data":{"timestamp":" 1549113753066"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_154127"," gameId":" 40fb569e-ea12-4cd7-be2b-0fcd50886535"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}